# NAFISA ANJUM

1920 NE Terre View Dr. I108, Pullman WA 99163 • 646 479 5736 • nafisaanjum9@gmail.com • www.nafisaanjum.com

### ABOUT ME

I am a graphic designer and illustrator from Bangladesh currently living in the Pacific North West. I have a passion for creating bold illustrations, calming hand-lettered work, and expressive typography. I am a hardworking and motivated individual who has a deep passion for Art and Design with emphasis on Digital Media. I have taken courses to gain skills and to prepare for creative collaborations. I have an excellent track record of academic performance and have acquired strong soft skills in communication, teamwork, and leadership from my work experiences and other social activities.

#### **EDUCATION**

## 2018- 2021 Bachelor of Fine Arts | School of Arts & Sciences | Washington State University

#### **DESIGN SKILLS**

 Adobe Photoshop Adobe InDesign

• Adobe Illustrator

- After Effects
  Typography
- Procreate Product Design
- Isadora
- Adobe Premiere Pro
  Figma

- Logo Design
- Merchandising

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- Critical thinking
- Reliable & Professional
- Organized
- Public Speaking
- Time Management
- Leadership Skills
- Team Player
- Motivated

## EXPERIENCE

#### Freelance Graphic Designer | 2018-Present

- Designed logos, stickers, t-shirts, websites, other branding and communication materials for books and magazines.
- · Communicated with clients to gain a better understanding of their project and to assisted them in making their brand's design unique, effective, and appealing.
- Revised design briefs to meet client's budget and ideas to assist in their objectives into design concepts
- Created graphic representations of brands for 12 clients.

## Learning Assistant - World Art History | Fine Arts | Washington State University | 2021

- Delivered weekly teaching for 45 undergraduate students for Art History course.
- · Acted as the first point of contact for problems and inquiries for students in class.
- Effective organization skills to prioritize appropriate teaching and administrative duties.
- · Supervised studio work and provided advice on skills, methods, and approaches to assist the transfer of knowledge.

## Clerical Assistant II | Washington State University | 2018-2021

- Labeled, scanned, and digitized articles, archives, and photos to the school's library website for research.
- Trained and overseen 20 undergraduate employees, helped new hires, office temps, and part-time students.
- · Conducted monthly meetings to demonstrate progress to the whole team.
- Answered and directed calls, including taking messages, and making phone calls on behalf of the company.

### Graphic Design Mentorship | 2021

 For six months, I worked with a Graphic Design professor to learn how to use various digital media softwares and strategies.

## Artist's Talk | Fine Arts 101 | 2021

• Gave a presentation to a group of 70 undergraduate students about my work, my process, and influences as an artist. Through this lecture and one-on-one interactions, I helped them reach their full academic and social potential.

## Design Internship | 2020

• Collaborated one-on-one with a client to design an 18x24 painting that they entirely personalized.

#### Design Internship | 2021

• Completed a week-long, one-on-one collaboration with a client utilizing Curricular Practical Training (CPT) for a logo design for a prospective brewery that combined statistical and design concepts.